

Piotr Skrzypa

Senior Unity Developer



+48 723 497 731



skrzypapiotr144@gmail.com



in linkedin.com/in/piotr-skrzypa



github.com/PiotrSkrzypa



piotrskrzypa.github.io

Summary

For 8 years, I have been creating games with Unity, including over 6 years professionally. I have worked on productions for mobile platforms, PC, VR, and consoles. I have participated in the full game development cycle — from designing architecture, through implementing mechanics and user interfaces, to debugging and optimization. I also have experience in managing development teams and creating developer tools.

Skills

- Unity
- Visual Studio
- C#
- GIT
- Addressables
- Shader Graph
- VFX Graph

- UniTask
- Zenject
- UniRx / R3
- Odin Inspector
- Porting to consoles
- Teamwork

Experience

Simplicity Games, Programista Unity3D, November 2017 – February 2018

- **Ski Jump Challange** (Android, iOS)
 - o Created the user interface based on the designer's guidelines
 - Collaborated with teams of developers, artists, and designers

Primebit Games S.A., Senior Unity Developer, February 2019 – Present

- Clash II (PC)
 - Led the development team
 - Created the entire game architecture
 - Created a map editor for the design team
 - o Optimized memory usage using Profiler and Memory Profiler, implemented resource loading with Addressables
 - Developed a unit management system
 - Developed a unit skill system
 - Developed a unit equipment system

 Developed a UI window management system and animations using the DOTween library

• Inside Grass (Android, iOS)

Fixed existing bugs

• 8 Minute Empire (Nintendo Switch)

 Ported a mobile game to the Nintendo Switch platform, including adding gamepad support, adjusting controls, and user interface

• Caveman Chuck (Nintendo Switch)

- Ported a mobile game to the Nintendo Switch platform, including adding gamepad support, adjusting controls, UI, and save system
- Supervised the certification process

Dark Tower (Nintendo Switch)

- Ported a mobile game to the Nintendo Switch platform, including adding gamepad support, adjusting controls, UI, and save system
- Supervised the certification process

VRFitness (Samsung Gear VR)

- Developed two games for Samsung Gear VR headsets in collaboration with stationary bicycles and for an external client
- o Created a multiplayer module offering races with other players on a local Wi-Fi network
- Optimized performance to ensure smooth gameplay

Education

Computer Science, Master's Degree, Rzeszów University of Technology, February 2018 – July 2019

 Master's thesis: "Artificial Intelligence Algorithms Solving the Shortest Path Problem," grade: 5

Computer Science, Bachelor's Degree, Rzeszów University of Technology, October 2014 – February 2018

- Overall GPA: 4.6
- Bachelor's thesis: "Application of Artificial Intelligence Algorithms in Computer Games," grade: 5

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for the purposes necessary to carry out this and future recruitment processes pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).